# This class will contain and generate math questions.

# Methods
# 1. method to generate a math question from a list  of questions
@math_questions = [
  {
    question: "What is 5 + 7?",
    answer: 12
  },
  {
    question: "Subtract 9 from 20.",
    answer: 11
  },
  {
    question: "Multiply 3 by 4.",
    answer: 12
  },
  {
    question: "Divide 36 by 6.",
    answer: 6
  },
  {
    question: "Calculate 8 squared.",
    answer: 64
  },
  {
    question: "What is 15 minus 9?",
    answer: 6
  },
  {
    question: "Add 2.5 and 3.2.",
    answer: 5.7
  },
  {
    question: "Multiply 5 by 10.",
    answer: 50
  },
  {
    question: "Divide 45 by 9.",
    answer: 5
  },
  {
    question: "What is 14 plus 18?",
    answer: 32
  },
  {
    question: "Subtract 4 from 11.",
    answer: 7
  },
  {
    question: "Multiply 6 by 7.",
    answer: 42
  },
  {
    question: "Divide 72 by 8.",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: "Calculate 5 cubed.",
    answer: 125
  },
  {
    question: "What is 25 minus 17?",
    answer: 8
  },
  {
    question: "Add 3.7 and 2.4.",
    answer: 6.1
  },
  {
    question: "Multiply 8 by 9.",
    answer: 72
  },
  {
    question: "Divide 63 by 7.",
    answer: 9
  },
  {
    question: "What is 22 plus 14?",
    answer: 36
  },
  {
    question: "Subtract 8 from 15.",
    answer: 7
  }
]